cross,
before the
centuries
Ten
how
exactly
recorded
a song
clothes would
man's
a dying
up.
be divided
22.
Psalm
it in the
wrote
David
person,
first
was never
himself
but David
executed.
an old man.
died
He
else.
someone
describing
He was
Stripped,
surrounded,
poured out.
life
his
line.
Watch one
dying
the
He wrote that
divide his
killers would
man's
for
lots
cast
clothes and
them.
among
garments
They part my
upon
lots
them and cast
vesture.
my
later,
years
A thousand
it at the
watched
John
cross,
clothes,
Jesus's
dividing
soldiers
for the
lots
then casting
coat,
seamless
be
might
scripture
that the
fulfilled.
early,
years
A thousand
down,
it written
had
God
happened,
so when it
the cross was
know
you'd
accident.
no
plan.
It was the
Psalm
man of
The suffering
name,
22 has a
Jesus.
for the
dice
They rolled
his back,
off
clothes
he was
what
never seeing
doing,
really
his life to
down
laying
back.
win you